[Music]
reconciling bank statements has
traditionally been like solving a
timeconsuming puzzle with complex
transactions making it tough to fit the
pieces together Microsoft co-pilot and
Dynamics 365 business Central is your AI
powered bookkeeping assistant that helps
you turn a tedious monthly chore into a
quick review start by importing bank
statements into business Central for
co-pilot to analyze using built-in rules
and Power AI co-pilot Compares
transaction descriptions amounts and
dates to find matches in your Ledger
entries even when multiple charges are
Consolidated into a single
entry found a transaction that wasn't
accounted for such as interest or Bank
fees no problem co-pilot also suggests
GL accounts to post remaining
transactions to improving the accuracy
of your financial records and if you've
discovered a recurring payment co-pilot
helps you save the transaction pattern
for the next time solve the puzzle of
bank reconciliation faster and easier
than ever before with co-pilot in
business Central